Rise and shine.
Welcome to Morioh Radio,
Kai Harada, here,
keeping you company
on this fine morning.
And I've got just
the melody to start you off right…
Well, shall we dig in?
Of course. How could I forget…
JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
A demon's crept into
our everyday life
It's about to take away
something precious
Our peace has already
crumbled long ago
So casually, so nonchalantly
It's taken from us
before we know it
If we want it back,
now's the chance
With the sharpness of
the piercing arrow
The beauty of two souls united
Wherever you go, chase you
Whenever, chase you
I will chase you
Nowhere to escape
Start running, I will chase you
Tomorrow, chase you
My fists will be the one
to show you
Tenacity decides
who will win or lose
So I chase you
EPISODE 21
YOSHIKAGE KIRA JUST
WANTS TO LIVE QUIETLY, PART 1
Mr. Kira… Um, Mr. Kira?
Mr. Kira, if you have nothing else to do,
would you like to have lunch with us?
My apologies, but I must decline.
These documents need delivering.
Cheerio.
Don't waste your time!
He'll just end up
being the downer of the group.
Every time we've had him come along,
you can't tell if he's
happy or completely miserable…
Yoshikage Kira, age 33, single.
He really is the consummate worker,
but, man, the guy is
dull as dishwater.
He's not necessarily a bad guy,
it's just he has no personality.
Well, someone's a little
bent out of shape…
SAVORY BREAD / GARLIC BREAD /
APPLE PIE / SLICED BREAD / MILK BREAD / RUSKS /
CROISSANTS / DONUTS /
PIZZA BREAD / CORNBREAD
Those new girls at work
invited me to lunch, that's all.
I promised you
lunch was our time together.
CHOCOLATE MUFFINS
I'd never leave you
to go with them.
You heard me turn them down,
didn't you?
CHOCOLATE MUFFINS
SLICED BREAD / CROISSANTS
Have I ever left you
by your lonesome?
Now, stop this silly fretting,
and let's pick out
some sandwiches.
KATSU SANDWICH
Now, which one do you want?
It has such a delicate texture,
doesn't it?
This bakery makes its sandwiches
with bread it bakes fresh at 11 AM;
they're all the rage.
You'd be lucky to
find one on the shelf after 1 PM.
You can feel they're fresh
from the oven through the wrapper.
The katsu they use is
always freshly fried and perfectly crispy.
Look at that…
You tore the wrapper
and made a mess.
Such a naughty girl.
But now this sandwich is ruined,
we'll just buy
the one underneath.
Thank you for dropping by.
Beautiful, isn't it?
Quaint, little Morioh…
It might just be the most
marvelous town on earth…
It's like we're on a picnic.
A bit aromatic…
I think it maybe time
we part ways…
The end is close at hand.
"Close at hand"…
Perhaps I'll cross paths with some
new girl visiting from out of town.
Just some dog…
Shigechi!
Oyo?
Josuke, Okuyasu!
Hey, perfect timing, Shigechi.
Let me get right to the point,
we need to borrow some lunch money.
We forgot to bring it.
Huh? What are you talking about?
What happened to all
that money from the lottery?
We deposited all that.
You think we're gonna go all
the way to the bank
just for some lunch money?
A thousand yen will be enough
for both of us.
Yeah.
Come on…
As soon as class is
out we'll head straight to the bank.
Hey, I know that logo…
You got a sandwich from St. Gentlemen!
So they weren't sold out?
Well, you're not gettin' any!
It's mine.
Oh, all right.
I'll lend you the thousand yen…
Now we're talkin'!
Thank you!
I'm writing an i.o.u. for this,
no weaseling out of this one.
Me? You're the biggest weasel
there is!
- Let's see… "June 24th."
- We owe you one, Shigechi.
- "Lent 1,000 yen" … Lent?
- Later!
Now how do you write
the character for "lent" again?
Lent…
LENT
Well, this'll work.
Hiragana works just as well.
I don't know the characters
for "Josuke" or "Okuyasu" either.
Huh?
M-My sandwich…
W-Where'd it go?
Ah, there it is.
I don't remember it
being this faraway, but oh well.
Th-That's…
Hey, Josuke, Okuyasu, wait!
I need your thumbprints
on my i.o.u!
Your thumbprints!
What is that little punk
squealing about?
He took my bag by accident…
Ah, could you be any more annoying.
How the hell do we do that?
You know, you cut your thumb
with a knife…
Okay, now you've gone too far.
Just sign it okay, sign it.
Come on, let's get our asses
to St. Gentlemen. They'll sell out.
Dammit. If he sees
what's in that bag…
She's wearing the ring
I bought her.
It has my fingerprints…
The police will open
an investigation…
It's just a matter of time before
they trace the ring back to me.
Yoshikage Kira has left
not a single clue in fifteen years.
And a pathetic brat
isn't changing that!
Josuke, come on.
Okay.
I'll wait outside.
Now, what to do?
Seize by force it is.
On second thought,
better I snatch it without his knowing.
Shigechi!
You lucky son of a gun.
The St. Gentlemen sandwiches
were already sold out! Shit!
Oh, so they're sold out.
I feel really sorry for you guys.
I guess I could sell you mine
for 10,000 yen.
There's not a decent bone
in your body is there?
Well, Hokaben it is, then, Josuke.
Hokaben, huh?
Nothing we could get for
500 yen and a drink
could ever fill us up.
The cafeteria'll give us plenty of food.
'Sides, Koichi said he'd
get lunch at the cafeteria today.
No way! He'll be eating
with Yukako Yamagishi, right?
Why do I have to be the third wheel
to those honeymooners' lovefest?
What's worse, the school serves
one-millimeter-thick meat,
and who knows what
the hell they put in that miso soup?
Hey, the equipment room at
my middle school's gym
has a ton of drinks.
Our P.E. teacher always sneaks away
to have coffee and tea in there.
All of the teachers are in
the faculty room during lunch,
so I sneak in through the window
sometimes and take some.
Why don't you guys go buy a lunch
and we'll go there together.
You're stealing from school?
You are a stingy bastard.
You can't even buy your own drinks?
You'll never see me
do something that greedy.
See ya!
I was just trying to be nice…
Okay. You better pay me back
my thousand yen tomorrow!
Oh, I'm very sorry, sir!
I wasn't looking where I was going.
Really sorry.
Shit, shit…
He's left his idiotic friends,
but he's heading back to school.
He's going to eat lunch at school…
What to do?
BUDOGAOKA MIDDLE SCHOOL
So they call him "Shigechi"…
There's no question…
In a matter of minutes,
he will open that bag…
This is unfathomable.
Yes, yes… No one's gonna
bother me and my lunch in here.
Oh yeah, that's right!
Before I eat,
I need to make my coffee.
I didn't come all the way here
for nothing.
How very fortunate, Shigechi.
Had you peaked inside,
I would've had to obliterate you.
Hey, Josuke! We're here!
- It's smaller than I thought…
- W-What?
They're not supposed to be here!
Shigechi, you here?
Shigechi!
Oh, what're you and Josuke
doing here?
We decided we couldn't
pass up some coffee from cafe gym.
We got 500-yen Makunouchi bentos!
Hmph. This after
you called me a greedy thief…
Self-righteous pricks!
Come on, give us a break.
Haven't you heard of people
changing their minds?
What to do?
Offing one of them
would be a picnic, but not three.
Shit!
And she's only centimeters away…
Shigechi, don't forget
my drink, too.
No coffee for me.
Make it green tea.
Got any black tea?
I want some milk in it.
Blech. Makunouchi with milk tea?
That's gross.
Shit! He's gonna eat right
on top of this thing.
At this rate, he's going to
open the bag in front of all of them!
Aw, soy sauce again.
They always put soy sauce
with katsu.
Huh? You always eat katsu
with soy sauce.
What?! You jackass!
Everyone knows
it's tonkatsu sauce!
Putting soy sauce on
tonkatsu violates all that is sacred.
Who cares?
Yes!
W-What?
Dammit!
What?
MORIOH LANDMARK #7
"BAKERY ST. GENTLEMEN"
HOW TO GET THERE: TAKE THE "MORIOH
BUDOGAOKA HIGH SCHOOL" BUS
TO ITS FINAL STOP AND
WALK TWO MINUTES ON
THE GREEN ROAD FROM THE STATION.
STUDENTS, HOUSEWIVES,
AND OFFICE LADIES RAVE ABOUT
ITS VARIETY OF STONE-OVEN BAKED BREADS.
DON'T MISS THEIR BEST SELLER:
SANDWICHES. BEWARE, THEY SELL OUT FAST.
Dammit!
What?
Hey! Just what do you
think you're doing, Josuke?
Hey! It looks a lot like
someone trying to steal a sandwich to me.
No! Quit being so stupid.
I thought I heard something weird,
I was just gonna take
a quick look.
It's totally off limits!
I know you wouldn't just
look at it!
Teriyaki chicken sandwiches
are my favorite,
give me a teeny-weeny
bite, is exactly what you'll say.
You sure are
a greedy little stinker, aren't you?
Where the hell's my tea? Remember?
Milk tea for me.
I'm making them.
Now!
I did it.
Get 'em while they're hot.
One green tea and one milk tea.
Ooooh…
Thank you!
What's with you?
M-My sandwich?
What'd you do with it?
Huh? Oh…
So it is gone.
But we don't know what
happened to it, right, Okuyasu?
Yeah.
All right, enough of the games!
You have to know.
You're the only ones here!
No, seriously, we don't!
Really, we're not messing around.
No joke, we really
don't know what's going on.
Y-You ass wipes…
I-I'm gonna get really mad!
It's the truth!
All right, I've had about enough.
Why would we take your sandwich—
Lie all you want,
I'll find out soon enough!
All I have to do is have
Harvest turn this room inside out!
Damn you're annoying!
Fine, do it!
I want you to!
Look all you want.
You think we'd steal
that stupid thing?
What? I can't see what
they're doing from in here.
What is that little pissant up to?
Hey!
I know somebody's in here!
It's the P.E. teacher!
It's time to bail, Shigechi!
B-But my sandwich!
Now's not the time!
You wait!
Damn, snot-nosed kids.
I thought my tea and
coffee wasn't lasting very long.
I thought I was going crazy.
No wonder.
I gotta start locking
this sucker up like Fort Knox.
Much ado about nothing…
I beat the odds,
and got back my girl.
I've always had this feeling…
That looking over Yoshikage Kira's
shoulder is a guardian angel…
That living each and every
day with rigor and boldness,
will deliver me from
a life of unhappiness.
That was close.
I knew you'd come back to me.
Found it!
Now why is there
a stranger holding my sandwich?
And why is there some strange man
hanging around my middle school?
You wouldn't happen to
be talking to me, would you, little boy?
Because I have not the slightest idea
what you're going on about.
This is my sandwich.
I just purchased the item
at St. Gentlemen.
Wrong, that bag belongs to me!
And I have my reasons
for saying so!
Not that you'd ever understand.
It's time to take back
what's ours, Harvest!
W-What? What's happening?
They're pulling my bag…
W-Wha—?! W-What…
My sandwich…
Is this… a real hand from
a real person?
Low and behold.
You've seen what you cannot unsee.
And it seems, little boy,
that you and I share a unique power.
You can see my Harvest?
H-Hey, what's this hand?
Why are you walking around
with a hand in your bag?
You are by yourself now,
I presume? Your two friends…
I believe you referred
to them as Josuke and Okuyasu?
Shall I assume they have
a similar power?
Hey! You stay right there!
If you so much as blink,
you're a goner!
You're a super weirdo!
And I don't want you
coming any closer!
You're really starting to
make my skin crawl!
Don't move!
I said stay right there!
I'm Yoshikage Kira, age 33.
I live in northeast
Morioh's villa district,
and I am not married.
I work for Kameyu department stores,
and I return home
no later than 8 PM.
I don't smoke,
but enjoy the occasional libation.
I'm in bed by 11 PM,
and am sure to sleep
a solid eight hours.
If I indulge in
a warm glass of milk
then stretch for
about twenty minutes,
sweet, sweet dreams
are usually the result.
I awake like a newborn
baby, refreshed and recharged.
I was given a clean
bill of health at my last checkup.
W-What is all this about?!
I have lived my life in pursuit
of inner peace.
I choose not to concern myself
with winning or losing,
life's troubles, or enemies
who bring sleepless nights.
That is my social-coping mechanism,
and that is what brings me happiness.
Of course, if I were ever to
engage in combat, I would never lose.
In other words, Shigechi,
you are a troublemaker
who could hinder my sleep.
You are the enemy.
Th-That's…
Deadly Queen…
I named him myself.
Before you utter a word of this
to another soul,
I will eradicate you.
I will sleep soundly tonight.
EPISODE 22
YOSHIKAGE KIRA JUST
WANTS TO LIVE QUIETLY, PART 2